Hello everyone! I'm Hitomi Takamatsu from Equal Love!
Yes! So, this is the fifth edition of the Equal Love Boat Racing Club!
What a surprise today!
Ta-da!
We're here at Boat Race Hama no Kozan!
Yes!
We've come all the way to Shizuoka Prefecture! Thank you very much.
Last time at Toda-san, even though Shoko won.
I had a negative result for life.
But this time, we've made a special expedition.
And today, as our guest, or rather...
I mean, she's here as a no-show candidate.
This is the girl! Come in!
Yes! I'm Mirinya, the unbranded candidate!
Please, take care of her!
Yay!
What a pain in the ass! Finally, Mirinya! Please take care of me! Yay! Meriya!
Finally, Miriya's here!
I'm in love!
I'm so happy! Koi-gan?
That's right! Because you look like you're having so much fun.
I've been thinking about it.
Really?
I'm glad, because I've always wanted to try it.
I'm so happy! And, you know, I've never been this far away from home before.
Yay!
I'll be at Boat Race Hamanaka today.
I'm going to do my best, and I'm going to do it alone.
We've come all this way, so we have to win.
So, the director wasn't here today, so...
Supervisor!
I'm thinking of asking him to call me for advice.
Right now? Maybe now?
The director? You're going to go straight to the director? I'll do it? I'm thinking of having him do it, but right now? Now?
To the director?
To the director.
Really?
It's like an assault on your life.
No? Really?
I do.
Yes, I do.
I'll just have a quick call.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
Take a call.
I'm getting nervous.
Wait, I'm getting nervous.
I'd like to make a phone call to the director for advice.
Thank you very much.
Your call has been connected to the director.
That's great.
Mr. Yoshihara.
Good morning.
We're here at Boat Race Hamanaka today.
Amazing! Finally, we haven't won anything.
I'm not winning! I'm here even though I'm losing.
Do you have any advice for us, Mr Hamanaka? Director.
Yes, please.
What's with all the women today?
That's right. It's a ladies' match.
That's right. I heard some rumours.
Yes. - Yes.
The ladies' match is...
Yes, sir.
I heard that the Inn doesn't always run away.
What? Is that so?
I heard it from a betting man I used to beat.
But I don't know if I'm winning with him or not.
But I heard it's a common theory.
Oh, so you're saying that there might not be a lot of in? It depends, but I heard it's a common theory.
It means that there may not be a lot of in.
Basically, boats get in.
Yes, they do.
But the ladies don't, apparently.
I didn't know that.
That's good news.
Look at that.
There you go.
Let's do it together.
I'll do it.
I'll do my best.
It's Milinya's first time at a boat race.
Yes, Milinya's here, too.
It's her first race.
Stop it.
I'm glad... that Milinya's racing boats, too.
Listen to Hitomi's advice.
I'll make sure she listens to me.
We'll race together today.
I'll win and go home.
If I don't, I'll...
Not the bullet train.
What? What?
Take the Donko and come home.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'll go home slowly.
Good luck.
Thank you, Mr. Tato Ciaro.
Yes, yes, 10 years.
Thank you.
That's great.
Leading information.
Can I show you this?
The staff member we were just talking to here, Sashiara-san...
That Axter... it's huge.
Big Axter, you've been here all day.
Soul, soul, thank you.
But I've heard great things! Yeah! Yes, for sure!
It's not always about the yin.
The first boat is basically stronger.
Have you heard that?
Maybe not.
Oh! That's right! It doesn't work that way!
It might!
Then I'll take that into account!
I'll think about it! Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you! So, here are the rules.
This time, we're asking for 20,000 yen for each member of the war fund.
20,000 yen.
That's great.
That's 100,000 yen.
Right?
20,000 yen today!
That's a lot of money!
That's pretty impressive.
Yay!
We'll have six races this time.
I'm going to do six races this time.
In total, you'll have to spend all your 20,000-yen boat tickets.
In the rock race.
Understood.
It's okay to spend a lot on something you're moderately confident about.
And if you have any money left over at the end of the race,
I will save it as a component of the boat racing club.
I'd love to save it.
You really should.
We're in the red, aren't we?
Yes, we are. I'm sorry.
I've never saved anything.
I'll do my best today. You're in the red, right? Yes, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I've never told you directly.
I'll do my best today.
This time, you know, I usually do three or four races,
Today I can do six.
So it's probably my first time, but I'll get used to it.
I'll get used to it.
I'll be fine.
I'm nervous.
This time I'm here on the first day of the ladies' race, the Venus S Round 10, the Monthly Boat Race Cup, and it's my first ladies' race.
I see. So it's only women. Only women. But I like the ladies' races.
Why was that?
I know the female players better and there are a few players who are participating today that I want to support,
So I thought today would be a good day, because you're really sparkling.
You look like you can do it.
It's important to have a good spirit, isn't it?
Yes, it's important.
Because we are women, we can communicate with each other, can't we?
I think so.
I'm sure we can win today. So I've been looking into the trends of Boat Race Hamanako, and I heard that the course at Lake Hamanako has the widest competition surface in the country.
It's true that it's very wide, and the previous Boat Race Toda has a higher belt ratio than the national average, and it's also easy to make a decision to roll up and stab.
Maybe I don't need to aim for one today! It's a basic one, maybe with a moto race. Let's try to think, like you like, on a hunch?
Just go with your gut.
Are you still learning?
I don't know.
But just go with your gut and learn as you go, okay?
I'll do that.
I will.
I have a gut feeling too.
So, without further ado.
I'll start with my predictions for the five races.
My strategy today is...
I know a lot of female riders, and I support a lot of them.
I have a favourite, and I want to give her my full support in the races she's in.
Millinya has a nice box, I think it's called the 315 Millinieux Box.
I want to buy it.
I'll buy it.
If 3 or 5 come first, it'll be terrible.
It'll be great!
Oh, no.
That's terrible.
The 315 box for your birthday on 15 March in the Millinyu box and the
And a double box of my pupils.
I'm going to run this on all the rents.
I'm on it.
I feel like I'm on a roll.
But I just talked to him. There's a lot of 315 boxes.
Is there?
Yeah.
Yeah? - Yeah.
It's coming.
Aah! I might do it.
Then let's do it in earnest right away. First up is Maki Nagashima. I've seen your name in so many places.
That's amazing! With Maki Nagashima,
Noda Meizuki.
Wait a minute.
Are they the same?
I always call her Meigetsu-chan on my own.
Noda Meigetsu.
I think she's here.
I've been pushing her a lot recently. She's 23 years old, so I want to support her.
I want to support her, and she'll be in race 7.
Sorry, there was another one.
Cute!
Moeimi.
I've seen her name in so many races,
She's very strong.
I don't know.
So, cute Moeimi.
Wow, you must be watching her a lot. I'm sure.
You usually watch boat races.
Yes, I do.
She knows a lot.
I asked my father about the forecast today.
Hitomipapa.
I'm going to take that into account as well.
That's reassuring.
It's the first day, you never know.
First day?
I don't know.
You don't know.
You never know.
Any numbers ring a bell?
Five races.
Three.
Three's good.
Two, three.
Two or three?
Me too.
Two, three, one, two, three.
There we go.
Wait, I don't understand.
One, three is what I'm trying to do.
They're teaching me so much!
Okay, Mirin, you can go.
Okay, go!
Mirin's teaching me so much.
It's the first time I'm doing it.
If you don't mind, please press the issue button.
One at a time?
Wait, we're supposed to buy 6,000 of these.
Wait!
Help me.
Wait, wait, wait, I just made a mistake!
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry!
Please press the Enter or Pay Sessor button.
What?
Bug card, down.
What? Did I just insert two cards?
Oh, I made a mistake! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
I thought you were going to say something like that.
I'm sorry! No, 20,000 yen.
It didn't feel like 20,000 yen, it felt like 10,000 yen.
But it doesn't matter, it's all right.
Yes, so I bought it.
Miri-no, Miri-no, you can buy it, you can buy it.
Money!
Oh, I have money, spend 10,000 yen.
Spend 10,000 yen.
OK!
Sweat, sweat, sweat, sweat... what's in the sweets? What's in the sweets? What's in the sweets?
What's in the sweets?
What's in the sweets? What's in the sweets? I'm glad I didn't have time to make the change.
I'm getting a slant.
What?
You didn't change it correctly.
Sir, you didn't change it correctly.
What happened?
I changed the manager to 4646123.
But it only had 1 in it.
What do we do, we're closed. We're closed, right?
Pitcher, well, that means there's a 1 coming in.
If I get 4646123, I'm going home.
I'm not going home, I'm not going home, I'm not going home, I'm not going home, I'm not going home, I'm not going home. I'm in formation with these eyes and 464612321.
What about Mirinya?
I'm with the 315 Mirinya box,
I also bought a trifecta with 461.
Yay!
I really couldn't have done it without you,
I know I made a mistake, but thank you.
Next time I can do it more calmly. I really did it thanks to you all, so I'm making my own mistakes, but thank you.
Next time I can do it more calmly.
It's starting!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Busy day!
Busy!
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Oh, my God!
It's starting!
Oh, my God.
Where's Sashiara?
I'm with Mr. Sashiara.
By the way, the director...
4646 years ago.
345156 is the director.
That's why...
I'm the one who said 4646123!
Awww!
Monster!
Why is that?
Do you round me up?
Well, of course you do.
I'll be in shock, I'll be in shock.
I'll be shocked if he comes, director.
He's looking at Motoki very seriously.
The wind's picking up.
The sound is so powerful. It's so close.
So close. I'm so happy to see it so close.
It's starting! It's starting! Draws! It's starting!
Keep up the good work! Keep up the good work!
What? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? What?
Oh, no 6, no 6, no 6.
Six is not coming. Six is not coming anymore.
Maybe it's a four.
It changes so much at the corners. Oh! It's coming! Go for it!
Oh, he's so fast! Very fast!
Oh, but there's a 2 coming, there's a 2 coming.
Oh, yeah, 2!
I haven't won two!
Two is coming!
Oh, but!
Six?
Six, two!
Oh, 2's amazing!
Oh, I'm in heaven!
Oh, but I can't be bothered with 2, it's too hard.
Two, two!
Oh, it's capsized.
Oh, but this one, too.
Are you all right?
This one's capsized, so there's no more fighting.
We're going to finish in the order that we came in.
Basically.
Okay.
It's dangerous, so we'll jump around.
I didn't do two.
No, no, no.
There's a two.
There's two.
You're not gonna win one.
Two.
Two, six, four.
Oh, two again.
Two or two.
Two.
Six.
Four.
We lost.
Yes, we lost big.
I lost a lot.
I lost 2,300 yen.
I'm...
But I bought the wrong one, so it's 1,200 yen.
Oh!
I'll get it back.
It's not much.
It's amazing, it's so powerful.
It's so fast.
It's so fast!
It doesn't matter if you're a woman or a man, you're still so fast!
It was so cool!
Is this the second time? And that rock race.
I'll definitely win!
I'm gonna win!
I'm on fire!
Let's go!
You're good!
Good! Good!
You're A1.
But 1 or 3?
Can you do it?
Oh, wait, I made a mistake.
I've wasted so much paper today.
I'll take these home and use them as notepads.
The Takamatsu family has about 100 of these mark sheets at home.
The Takamatsu family has about a hundred of these mark-sheets at home when they receive phone calls.
Really.
I'm taking this home with me today, aren't I?
Sorry, I made a mistake.
But there's only two more races in the first half.
That's a lot.
Can I put it on?
Yeah, it's okay.
Okay.
Assuming that one chance 113 comes along, I'm really rooting for Moe Cute from the bottom of my heart in this race.
All morning.
We'll go from three in formation.
Three.
You've been saying that all morning.
It's Bob, Moe Kawaii.
She's 23.
He's like a friend.
It's too selfish, but...
It's too selfish, but I think of him as a friend.
I think of her as a friend.
That's how I want to support you.
Even if 3 go...
It's easier for the outsiders to come.
Then...
Supervisor...
2-6.
3-24-15-6.
You're a pro.
Wait a minute, that's me.
May I? You'll be wearing it. With the director.
I'll start with Moe, so 3 people for 4,000 yen.
Is that okay?
Sasahara-san is doing it with me.
But I only spent 1,000 yen from earlier.
I can spend a lot.
I think I have 9,000 yen left.
What do you think?
I think I'll end up with about 4,000 yen.
Eh...
It's fine.
I don't know.
But, like, your age...
Or a name or something.
That's right.
Even Tashibara-san is chosen by his face.
That's part of it, too.
Directors tend to make decisions based on faces.
Mihiya too.
That's possible.
We're close in age.
What, 19?
The player from No. 5 pavilion.
You're young.
Nineteen?
That's a wide range, isn't it?
All right, then.
After you.
I'm going to buy.
This time, I just spent 20,000 yen.
I just put in 20,000 yen all at once.
This time, I brought exactly the same amount.
I got the formation wrong this time, but I didn't win.
I only bought 1,000 yen, so I have a lot of money left.
This time, I'll bring 4,400 yen all at once.
OK, it's perfect!
Thank God, I made a mistake.
No change.
Yes, I'll win this one.
This time it's Hitomi.
I thought Hitomi might have a chance.
And if a doublet of 1 and 3 came, it would be worth thousands of yen, not hundreds, so I bought 400 yen.
And then, at the beginning of the game
2,6 from 3, all of them!
No, I'm pretty confident about this.
I can buy it calmly.
I'm glad. Good.
Good.
I can buy it!
I thought I had put out a proper buy.
Mr P bought 3, 1, 5 boxes,
But then I saw the pre-race start display earlier, and I thought about it for a minute.
I thought he was good.
A lot of people thought he was good.
Confident, aren't you?
Yes, I do.
More than just praying it's not too rough.
Now we just need a formation.
I've never done a formation before.
I'm so excited.
The rock race is about to begin.
Here we go.
This is a bit unrelated, but...
I forgot to wear my Equal Love Boat Racing Club T-shirt again today.
I'm really sorry.
Only the staff are wearing them.
Everyone else is wearing it and I forgot about it.
I'll wear it next time.
This T-shirt isn't cute.
You made it pretty.
Have it made.
I put a lot of effort into it.
Autorezm.
Oechan is starting.
Rocles.
Go for it!
Good luck with that. Come on! Come on! Come on! They're coming, they're coming! They're coming!
Now, that's a huge recommendation!
Oh, my God! Highly recommended!
Three is outstanding!
Come on!
I'm sending you a box, guys!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
Highly recommended! Highly recommended! I don't know!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Grandma! Granny!
Grandma! Grandma!
Grandma!
Oh, no!
Two's the key. Two's the key.
Second place, ah, ah, ah, ah, who? What's going on? Who's who? What colour?
What is that? Oh, my God! Oh, there's a Minion box! What? Minion box is coming!
The Minion box is coming!
Oh, no, no, no! It's the Minion Box, for sure!
The minion box is coming!
Here we go! We did it!
We did it! Oh, my God, they're here!
It's coming!
The minion box is here!
I should've bought more!
I'm betting on more.
More! Congratulations, one!
Four, three, five, one.
Oh, no!
That's Mignan's max.
Here it comes! It's my first Mirinyan MAX.
I hit it!
Yay!
Ishiko, 3, 5, 1, right?
It'll come on, I think.
How much are you buying, 200 yen?
Tsukutsu tsukutsu? I'm tsukutsu, maybe 1, what's the price, 200 yen?
It's gonna stick, right?
Is it on?
Then we'll see.
Ready?
Whoo-hoo!
What's going on?
Whoo-ah!
What?
And it's Kakemi 2.
Whooaaa!
Eeeee!
Oh, my God! It's the best! Ya-Ya-Ya-Ya-Ya-Ya-Ya-Ya-Ya! Oh, man! Oh, man!
Oh, no!
50,000 yen!
50,000 yen back!
That's great!
Yeah!
Seriously?
This is so bad.
Here comes the big one.
Sabourin box!
I'm so happy, Bonnabox, I'm so happy, let's go get a refund right away!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
Take it!
This is too much!
It's around here.
Capo's the best.
Oh, my God.
You got one of these?
Then put it in.
Put it in here.
Eeeee!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha! This is so bad, this is so bad. First time you've won something like this? First time! Yay!
He's going to tangle to the right!
Oh, my God! This is bad!
We got 50,300 yen back.
We've already won today.
We're winning this! We can buy it on the plus side, love.
We can definitely make a profit! We can definitely buy at a positive rate.
Does that mean we can spend a bit more?
Oh, no!
You mean I can spend more?
I can do more!
Yes!
That was crazy!
Thank you, 315 boxes.
Oh, that's nice.
Isn't Hitomi weak?
Rent to Hitomi.
Hey.
No, it's great.
I feel really happy.
Let's keep the momentum going in race 7.
Let's keep the momentum going for race 7.
It's going by so fast, isn't it, this seventh race is the first one I mentioned, with Natsuki Noda.
Acquaintance.
Yes, I know her.
She's at the Ichigo-tei.
I already believe in her.
This time, too.
Yes, I do.
I'd like to start with acquaintances.
Natsuki Noda is also 23.
Twenty-three.
We're about the same age.
Natsuki Noda is about the same age as you.
Right now, she's the most popular 3456.8 times in a row.
3456.8 times, 3456.8 times, the three favourites.
Popularity.
Three horses are the favourites and...
Three is coming.
But I'm from Noda.
She's my favourite.
Natsuki Noda, who I always root for, and who just came in second in the fifth, so she's the favorite this time.
I think she's going to come.
But it's said that wine won't come to the ladies' tournament.
I'm betting on Oshimen.
I'll start from the top.
Okay, Kokoro.
Sorry, Mike.
Oh, sorry! My ear's broken! The staff's ears are broken, and now I'm trying to do it like this, and it's like... Sorry, Mike, I'm so sorry! My ears are broken! My ear's broken!
I'm trying to do it like this, Gri! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, my ear!
How many would it be if you did it all in one go?
Twenty.
But one of them isn't that popular.
I'll go for it.
One front and all?
Yes.
Give it all to Mr. Noda.
All in! It's like a boat race! Put everything on Noda!
Cool!
Everything for Mr. Noda!
50,000 yen for Minia.
Good luck, Chief!
50,000 yen for Minia!
Show us how cool you are, boss.
I want to show you.
I want to show it to you.
Yes, sir.
One, zero, zero.
I bought 700 yen, Number 1.
Oda will pay for it.
Good.
Thank you.
Okay, I've changed it.
The girl I gave cancer to, here, looks like she's got a really painful bruise now. Even me? I deserved it.
It's amazing. The way I feel.
If you want to express your feelings for Kazuki Noda, you should do it.
I bought 700 yen this time with my eyes.
I want to come here soon.
And one day ago.
It's amazing. Already.
Anything is fine as long as Ichi comes.
Anything is fine as long as Noda comes through.
Today's race is a race that can be spared, so even if I lose more than usual, it's still fun.
It's great!
Okay, that's how I'm doing.
What about you, Mirinu?
I have 135 boxes.
The strongest box.
Strongest box again.
He's coming, isn't he?
It's coming!
It's possible. If it comes again, we're in trouble.
You bought 200 yen again, right?
Yes, I bought 200 yen. It's possible. It's possible! If he comes again, we're in trouble! He's buying 200 yen again!
Yes, he's buying 200 yen!
Yes, yes! It's possible!
I want him to come! I want to feel that feeling again!
Oh, no!
I know I'm not going to win this one, but I bought it on a hunch!
We're already in formation!
I hope you win!
I hope you win! It's the last one! The first half!
Just win! I want to win too.
How long can you stand there and not win?
I haven't really seen you win in this boat racing club.
Only about twice.
You can't win once?
In the first place, I've only guessed the race maybe twice.
Of those, almost God.
God.
Even though he's a human god.
It's amazing. I have a lot of knowledge.
Even if you only had knowledge.
With a serious manana attitude.
Director. Director.
Please watch over me.
I think the director has already retired. For today.
I think he's already retired for today.
Good luck, Meigetsu.
My position not at all.
That's right, it's in the public eye.
If the position doesn't come, I'm already...
I'll stay in the last race of the first half.
Here we go.
Good luck, sir.
That's great.
Fast, fast, fast.
Very fast.
Too fast.
It's fast, it's really fast!
That's so cool! Oh no! Oh, man, oh, man, oh, man. ...... Razwin!!!1,3,5 Go for it!
I did super!
1,3,5! Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
I'm just so nervous right now.
I can't talk anymore.
One, three, three, four, five.
Love cheese! Thank you!
Love cheese!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
That's great!
Yeah!
Congratulations!
You've done so much!
One bell!
Help me!
Two wins!
That's amazing! That's really great!
Congratulations!
You did it!
That's great!
Congratulations, Aisa! You did it! I'm so happy! That's great! Congratulations to Hitomi!
You did it!
How's it going?
2500...
Wait, what?
Two thousand five hundred and sixty.
Let's see...
200 yen!
5,000 yen!
Five thousand yen!
That's amazing! Congratulations!
But the impact is a bit too weak.
I'm sorry, I went 50,000 yen first, but the impact is a little too weak.
But the impact is a little too weak.
But I bought 4,700 yen.
Oh, wait a minute.
What?
I bought 4,700 yen, so that's 300 yen.
But I bought what I bought.
I won what I won.
I'm so happy I finally won.
I finally won!
A valuable refund.
It's a refund! I'll take it!
5120 yen!
It's back! It's back!
Wow!
We did it! We did it!
Milly's tenth best!
Ha-ha-ha, but we've been waiting for you! Milly's tenth best.
But I'm so happy.
That's great, great, great, really great.
Thank you very much, Azuki.
So the first three races of the first half of the season are over!
That was fun.
You've worked up a sweat already.
Too much noise.
I was so excited.
So I'm doing a tally for the first half.
First of all, I made a lot of noise.
Minus 5,180 yen.
Hey! How many times minus!
Well, well, well.
It's just the beginning.
I was about as excited as a big winner.
I was the one with the 50,000 yen.
Congratulations. And you were my favourite player.
I'm now at 49.7% recovery rate.
And Mirya's up 4,800 yen.
That's a 529.5% recovery rate.
A big win for you, isn't it?
I'm so happy.
I think we can do it again.
You should be as happy as I am.
Next time you win a moneybox...
Okay, okay, okay.
You don't have to be as loud as me, please.
I don't want to lose.
He's a really bad boy.
Okay, so, we've had such a blast.
We're all hungry now.
We're going to Hamanaka.
We'll have a boat race meal.
We thought we'd have some.
We're heading there directly now.
I'd like to have lunch there.
Well then, here we go!
Are you hungry too, Nyan?
I'm hungry!
But I heard a rumor that there are foods unique to Shizuoka and Boat Race Hamanaka...
I'm looking forward to it!
Boat race food is one way to enjoy boat races.
Yes, there are a lot of them, aren't there?
Yes, there is.
It's too much fun!
It's a lot of fun. Boat race tracks are fun.
Boat racetracks are fun.
Kids?
A place to play?
There's playground equipment.
It's great.
Kids' park?
They're playing so much.
It's so cute.
A kids' park in a boat race track?
Isn't that too new?
This place has ramen noodles and maharajas and a mid-park? Too new? What's this place?
Ramen noodles?
What's "Machala"?
Oh, I want some, I want some, I want some!
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's so cute! It's new!
I knew there was something wrong with Boch Lace.
It's suitable for families.
There's one like this, too.
It's so cute!
Oh, God, I'm so hungry.
I'm starving.
Looks delicious.
I've heard of this.
Is it a specialty?
Fujinomiya Yakisoba is a famous B-class gourmet yakisoba.
I want some of this too.
Nice.
It's really rare to see a food stall.
Lots of stalls.
You can eat local specialities.
But there's also a cafeteria up there.
I'd like to go there too.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Here! Ah! There she goes!
Cute.
Restaurant.
It's in!
Wow, that's like a boat restaurant.
Then I'd like to eat here today.
Yes! Yay! Ew! Ew! Ew! Oh, no! Eel! Unaju! There's no way we're going to eat here today.
Oh, no! Unagi! Unagi!
Eunju!
Wait! It's a boss race!
There's an eel!
Is the boss race only in Manako?
What do you think?
That's amazing!
Stop with the nudges!
Oh, my God! It's too gorgeous!
I want some! I'm in the mood for eel! Now!
Listen to this.
I heard you have to be a winner.
You can't eat it.
What?
We can't eat either?
We were so excited.
But we can't eat eels.
So you can only eat Mirinya?
Mirinya.
Just this bit of Mirinya.
Just this one bite.
Just a little bit of Mini-Nyan.
Can I have it?
No, thank you.
You're so kind.
I'll win the second half.
I'll eat here to cheer myself up.
Let's cheer up.
Thank you.
We can eat together.
Then let's go buy some Ammon first. Can we eat together? I'm looking forward to it! Thank you! Eels!
Ammon! Let's go buy some!
Oh, thank God! We can eat!
Yes! So I bought eels!
Wow!
Are you sure? Me too?
I see!
You can eat it?
I heard from the staff that you're going to win the second half.
Win?
You'll win! That's what they're counting on.
I'm under a lot of pressure because it's now.
But we'll have it, so we'll have it together.
Let's eat.
Thank you very much.
Yay! Bon appétit.
Then, let's have it.
Eels from the eel shop.
Seriously.
Yup. It's so delicious!
They look so tender!
You all must eat it when you come to Bočar Samonak's!
You must eat it!
It's really delicious!
We'll have the power to win after eating this!
We'll definitely win the second half, won't we?
Let's win!
We'll win!
So please, everyone, watch the second half!
Watch it!
Bye-bye!